The Observer Records UA062
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
The Observer Records
1975 -- 1984
1907 -- 1989
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
The Observer
UA062
13.2 Linear Feet 11 boxes
64 Digital Object(s)
The Observer collection contains photographs, negatives, and newspaper clippings from 1969-1988. The collection documents student journalistic research, photography, and publication.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into four series: Photographs; Article files; Research files; and Negatives.
Scope and Contents
The Observer collection contains photographs, negatives, and newspaper clippings from 1969-1988. It also contains research files of the Observer staff such as bulletins, brochures, correspondence, interviews, legal documents (e.g., findings of fact, depositions), memorandum, newsletters, pamphlets, planning documents, and reports. The collection represents the activities of student journalistic research, photography, and publication. The Observer staff organized material by subject headings.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Content Warning
This finding aid contains language that may be offensive or outdated. Because such language is in existing titles or direct transcription of materials, it has not been changed. Keeping this language intact provides the most accurate depiction of the creators' intent, and can potentially tell us important things about bigotry and bias on the part of the creators, or in a particular historical context. It can also preserve terms formerly applied by a group to self-identify that have since fallen out of common usage. For more information on DCA's content warning policy please visit our website.
Student Activities -- Student Publishing; Student life; Student activism; Student Activities -- Athletics; Curriculum and Instruction -- Faculty
- Observer photographs, 1907 -- 1989; UA062.001; 4.8 Linear Feet; 51 Digital Object(s)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains the photographs that probably constituted the Observer's photographic library including images from other sources. Files may also contain related material, such as brochures, graphics, negatives, programs, and reports. Subject headings include campus facilities, issues and events, faculty and staff, students, sports, and speakers. Many of the photographs are undated, so date ranges are not inclusive.
  Arrangement
  The photographs in this series are arranged alphabetically by file titles.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Admissions, UA062.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Archives, UA062.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Arena Theater, 1, UA062.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Arena Theater, 2, 1985 -- 1988; UA062.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
    - Student actors in the Arena Theater, 1988-09-01; UA062.001.001.00004.00001; Merwise, Steve (Box 1)
      Students; Student activities; Theater; Arena Theater
    - Students performing 'Execution of Justice', 1985; UA062.001.001.00004.00002; Unknown (Box 1)
      Tristan Boyer identified on back.
      Students; Student activities; Plays; Theater
  - Arena Theater, 3, 1985 -- 1989; UA062.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Ballou, 1907 -- 1987; UA062.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Barnum, 1975; UA062.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Bay Banks, UA062.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Bookstore, 1987 -- 1988; UA062.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Boston, 1983 -- 1987; UA062.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Boston Marathon, 1982; UA062.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Cabot IC Center, 1980 -- 1981; UA062.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Campaign for Tufts, 1980; UA062.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Campus, 1, 1979 -- 1986; UA062.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Campus, 2, 1982 -- 1984; UA062.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Campus - Boston, UA062.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Campus Center, 1983 -- 1988; UA062.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Cannon, 1977 -- 1982; UA062.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Carmichael, 1987; UA062.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Carpenter House Fire, 1979; UA062.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - Center Board, 1985; UA062.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Chayett, Neil, UA062.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Chemical Spill - Somerville, UA062.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - Cohen, 1987; UA062.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - Colcord (Dean), 1970 -- 1985; UA062.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
    - Dean Frank C. Colcord, 1970 -- 1985; UA062.001.001.00025.00001 (Box 1)
      photographic print; Colcord, Frank C.
    - Dean Frank C. Colcord, 1970 -- 1980; UA062.001.001.00025.00002; Morisseau, Stephen (Box 1)
    - Dean Frank C. Colcord, 1970 -- 1985; UA062.001.001.00025.00003; Rodgers, Richard (Box 1)
  - Comedy Show, UA062.001.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - Commencement, 1981 -- 1985; UA062.001.001.00027 (Box 1)
  - Computer Center, 1975 -- 1983; UA062.001.001.00028 (Box 1)
  - Cousens, 1981 -- 1983; UA062.001.001.00029 (Box 1)
  - CSL, 1981 -- 1986; UA062.001.001.00030 (Box 1)
    Contains negatives.
  - Curtis Hall, 1977; UA062.001.001.00031 (Box 1)
  - Dance, 1985; UA062.001.001.00032 (Box 1)
    - Fall dance concert, 1985; UA062.001.001.00032.00001; Krommes, Stephanie (Box 1)
      Students; Student activities; Dances and Dancing; Performances; Fall Dance Concert
  - Dance Marathon, 1984; UA062.001.001.00033 (Box 1)
  - Davis Square/Somerville, 1979 -- 1984; UA062.001.001.00034 (Box 1)
  - Daycare, 1984; UA062.001.001.00035 (Box 1)
  - Dining Hall, 1977 -- 1984; UA062.001.001.00036 (Box 1)
  - Divestment, 1983 -- 1985; UA062.001.001.00037 (Box 1)
  - Dormitories, 1975 -- 1981; UA062.001.001.00038 (Box 1)
  - Dreier, Peter, 1983; UA062.001.001.00039 (Box 1)
  - Eaton Lounge, 1982 -- 1986; UA062.001.001.00040 (Box 1)
  - Eliot Pearson, 1978; UA062.001.001.00041 (Box 1)
  - Ellis Oval, UA062.001.001.00042 (Box 1)
  - Environmental House, 1980; UA062.001.001.00043 (Box 1)
  - Faculty and Staff (A), 1980 -- 1986; UA062.001.001.00044 (Box 1)
  - Faculty and Staff (B), 1977 -- 1988; UA062.001.001.00045 (Box 1)
  - Faculty and Staff (C), 1969 -- 1981; UA062.001.001.00046 (Box 1)
  - Faculty and Staff (D), 1981; UA062.001.001.00047 (Box 1)
  - Faculty and Staff (E), 1981 -- 1983; UA062.001.001.00048 (Box 1)
  - Faculty and Staff (F), 1983 -- 1986; UA062.001.001.00049 (Box 1)
  - Faculty and Staff (G), 1975 -- 1981; UA062.001.001.00050 (Box 1)
  - Faculty and Staff (H), 1977 -- 1981; UA062.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Faculty and Staff (I, J), 1978 -- 1982; UA062.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Faculty and Staff (K), 1982 -- 1984; UA062.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - Faculty and Staff (L), 1976 -- 1982; UA062.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - Faculty and Staff (M), 1981 -- 1988; UA062.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Faculty and Staff (N), 1980 -- 1984; UA062.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Faculty and Staff (0), 1974 -- 1981; UA062.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Faculty and Staff (P, Q), 1981 -- 1982; UA062.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Faculty and Staff (R), 1981; UA062.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Faculty and Staff (S), 1979 -- 1986; UA062.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Faculty and Staff (T), 1971 -- 1982; UA062.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - Faculty and Staff (U, V, W, X, Y, Z), 1975 -- 1981; UA062.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1978 -- 1985; UA062.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - Fine Arts Building, UA062.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - Fletcher, 1971 -- 1981; UA062.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - Fraternity, 1988; UA062.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - Gallery Eleven, 1981 -- 1986; UA062.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - Goddard, 1984; UA062.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - Graffiti, UA062.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - Harvard Square/Cambridge, 1979 -- 1982; UA062.001.002.00020 (Box 2)
  - Hillside House, 1984; UA062.001.002.00021 (Box 2)
  - Hillside/Medford, 1972 -- 1984; UA062.001.002.00022 (Box 2)
  - Homecoming, 1979 -- 1985; UA062.001.002.00023 (Box 2)
    - Cheerleaders at homecoming, 1983-11-01; UA062.001.002.00023.00001; McGogh, Ken (Box 2)
      Cheerleading; Students; Homecoming
    - Crowd at homecoming, 1979; UA062.001.002.00023.00002; Triedman (Box 2)
      Homecoming; Students
    - Football team at homecoming, 1985-10-30; UA062.001.002.00023.00003; McGogh, Ken (Box 2)
      Athletics; Football; Homecoming; Dept. of Athletics
    - Students riding on float in homecoming parade, 1984; UA062.001.002.00023.00004; Thornton, Dan (Box 2)
      Homecoming; Parade floats; Students
    - Students walking with float in homecoming parade, 1984; UA062.001.002.00023.00005; Thornton, Dan (Box 2)
  - Hooper House/Health Services, 1980 -- 1986; UA062.001.002.00024 (Box 2)
  - Housing, 1983; UA062.001.002.00025 (Box 2)
  - IDC, 1982; UA062.001.002.00026 (Box 2)
    - Inter-Dormitory Council meeting in classroom, 1982-02-23; UA062.001.002.00026.00001; Sotiropoulos, Karen (Box 2)
      Student activities; Meetings; Dormitories; Student government; photographic print; Inter-Dormitory Council
    - Inter-Dormitory Council having a discussion, 1982; UA062.001.002.00026.00002; Edensword, Karen (Box 2)
      Student activities; Meetings; Dormitories; Student government; Students; Inter-Dormitory Council
    - Inter-Dormitory Council sitting at desks, 1982; UA062.001.002.00026.00003; Edensword, Karen (Box 2)
    - Inter-Dormitory Council, 1982-10-13; UA062.001.002.00026.00004; Izeman, M. (Box 2)
      Student government; Dormitories; Student activities; Students; Inter-Dormitory Council
  - Kid's Day, 1981 -- 1986; UA062.001.002.00027 (Box 2)
  - Mayer, Jean, 1976 -- 1983; UA062.001.002.00028 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous, UA062.001.002.00029 (Box 2)
  - Museum School, UA062.001.002.00030 (Box 2)
  - Music, 1980; UA062.001.002.00031 (Box 2)
    - Tufts University Chorale practicing Mozart, 1980-09-15; UA062.001.002.00031.00001; Morisseau, Stephen (Box 2)
      Student activities; Music rehearsals; Chorale
    - Beelzebubs standing around a car, 1980; UA062.001.002.00031.00002; Unknown (Box 2)
      Existence and Location of Copies
      A copy of this image was digitized as part of the Activities and organizations records and can be viewed in the Tufts Digital Library here: http://hdl.handle.net/10427/11717.
      Student activities; Music; A capella; Students; Beezlebubs
    - The Amalgamates, 1980; UA062.001.002.00031.00003; Thornton, Dan (Box 2)
      A copy of this image was digitized as part of the Historical Materials Collection and can be viewed in the Tufts Digital Library here: http://hdl.handle.net/10427/1593.
      Student activities; Music; A capella; Students; Amalgamates
  - Music at Tufts, 1985 -- 1986; UA062.001.002.00032 (Box 2)
    - Local band Cool Moon plays at Tufts, 1986-02-19; UA062.001.002.00032.00001; Unknown (Box 2)
      This is a local band.
      Music; Performances; Bands (Music)
    - Band plays at Tufts, 1985; UA062.001.002.00032.00002; Bushnell, Steven (Box 2)
  - Nichols House, UA062.001.002.00033 (Box 2)
  - North Hall, 1972; UA062.001.002.00034 (Box 2)
  - Nutrition, 1982; UA062.001.002.00035 (Box 2)
  - Observer, 1979 -- 1985; UA062.001.002.00036 (Box 2)
    - Staff of the Observer, 1985; UA062.001.002.00036.00001; Unknown (Box 2)
      Student activities; Publications; Newspapers; Students; Observer
    - Tufts Observer baseball team, 1985; UA062.001.002.00036.00002; Unknown (Box 2)
    - Tufts Observer staff, 1985; UA062.001.002.00036.00003 (Box 2)
    - Observer staff standing in front of a window, 1985; UA062.001.002.00036.00004; Unknown (Box 2)
    - Observer staff posing with newspapers, 1979; UA062.001.002.00036.00005; Unknown (Box 2)
  - Orientation Week, 1987; UA062.001.002.00037 (Box 2)
    - Peer advisors at orientation, 1987-09-04; UA062.001.002.00037.00001; Bushell, Steven (Box 2)
      Orientation; Students; College freshmen
  - Packard Hall, UA062.001.002.00038 (Box 2)
  - Peace Festival, 1983 -- 1986; UA062.001.002.00039 (Box 2)
  - PIRG, 1980 -- 1983; UA062.001.002.00040 (Box 2)
  - Progressive Organizations, Protests, People, 1981 -- 1989; UA062.001.002.00041 (Box 2)
  - Protest, 1979 -- 1987; UA062.001.002.00042 (Box 2)
  - Pub, 1981 -- 1986; UA062.001.002.00043 (Box 2)
  - Senate, 1980 -- 1987; UA062.001.002.00044 (Box 2)
  - Snow, 1978 -- 1983; UA062.001.002.00045 (Box 2)
  - Speakers (A), 1975 -- 1983; UA062.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Speakers (B), UA062.001.003.00002 (Box 3)
    Some date from: 1979-1984
  - Speakers (C), UA062.001.003.00003 (Box 3)
    Some date from: 1980-1985
  - Speakers (D), UA062.001.003.00004 (Box 3)
    Some date from: 1978-1984
  - Speakers (E), UA062.001.003.00005 (Box 3)
    No dated photos
  - Speakers (F), UA062.001.003.00006 (Box 3)
    Some date from: 1982-1985
  - Speakers (G), UA062.001.003.00007 (Box 3)
  - Speakers (H, I, J, K, L), UA062.001.003.00008 (Box 3)
    Some date from: 1976-1987
  - Speakers (M), UA062.001.003.00009 (Box 3)
    Some date from: 1983-1984
  - Speakers (N, O), 1983 -- 1984; UA062.001.003.00010 (Box 3)
  - Speakers (P, Q, R, S, T), 1983 -- 1984; UA062.001.003.00011 (Box 3)
  - Speakers (U, V, W), 1981 -- 1983; UA062.001.003.00012 (Box 3)
  - Sports: Aerobics, UA062.001.003.00013 (Box 3)
  - Sports: Baseball, 1981 -- 1987; UA062.001.003.00014 (Box 3)
  - Sports: Basketball (men's), 1979 -- 1985; UA062.001.003.00015 (Box 3)
  - Sports: Basketball (men's), 1979; UA062.001.003.00016 (Box 3)
  - Sports: Basketball (men's), 1979; UA062.001.003.00017 (Box 3)
  - Sports: Basketball (women's), 1979 -- 1985; UA062.001.003.00018 (Box 3)
  - Sports: Coaches, 1980 -- 1983; UA062.001.003.00019 (Box 3)
  - Sports: Coaches, 1980 -- 1985; UA062.001.003.00020 (Box 3)
  - Sports: Crew, 1979 -- 1985; UA062.001.003.00021 (Box 3)
  - Sports: Equestrian, UA062.001.003.00022 (Box 3)
  - Sports: Fencing, 1981 -- 1986; UA062.001.003.00023 (Box 3)
  - Sports: Field Hockey, 1978 -- 1986; UA062.001.003.00024 (Box 3)
  - Sports: Football, 1979 -- 1983; UA062.001.003.00025 (Box 3)
  - Sports: Football, 1983 -- 1987; UA062.001.003.00026 (Box 3)
  - Sports: Football, 1980 -- 1981; UA062.001.003.00027 (Box 3)
  - Sports: Football, UA062.001.003.00028 (Box 3)
  - Sports: Frisbee, 1980; UA062.001.003.00029 (Box 3)
  - Sports: Ice Hockey, 1979 -- 1982; UA062.001.003.00030 (Box 3)
  - Sports: Karate, UA062.001.003.00031 (Box 3)
  - Sports: Lacrosse (women's), 1981 -- 1986; UA062.001.003.00032 (Box 3)
  - Sports: Lacrosse (men's), 1985; UA062.001.003.00033 (Box 3)
    - Women's lacrosse team standing with Eastern College Athletic Conference trophy, 1985; UA062.001.003.00033.00001; Saferstien, Jon (Box 3)
      Athletics; Sports; Lacrosse (Women's); Awards; Eastern College Athletic Conference; Dept. of Athletics
  - Sports: Miscellaneous, 1980 -- 1981; UA062.001.003.00034 (Box 3)
    - Men's golf team, 1980; UA062.001.003.00034.00001; Unknown (Box 3)
      Athletics; Sports; Golf (Men's); Dept. of Athletics
    - Men's golf team posing with a flag, 1980; UA062.001.003.00034.00002; Unknown (Box 3)
    - Cheerleaders at basketball game, 1981-02-16; UA062.001.003.00034.00003; McGogh, Ken (Box 3)
      Cheerleading; Basketball (Men's); Sports; Dept. of Athletics
  - Sports: Rugby, 1986; UA062.001.003.00035 (Box 3)
    - Men's rugby game, 1986-04-09; UA062.001.003.00035.00001; Katagiri, Ejyo (Box 3)
      Athletics; Sports; Rugby; Dept. of Athletics
  - Sports: Sailing, 1972 -- 1986; UA062.001.003.00036 (Box 3)
  - Sports: Skiing, 1978; UA062.001.003.00037 (Box 3)
  - Sports: Soccer (men's), 1979 -- 1983; UA062.001.003.00038 (Box 3)
  - Sports: Soccer (men's), 1985; UA062.001.003.00039 (Box 3)
    - Men's soccer playing Bowdoin College, 1985; UA062.001.003.00039.00001; Thornton, Dan (Box 3)
      Athletics; Sports; Soccer (Men's); Dept. of Athletics; Bowdoin College
    - Men's soccer defending the goal, 1985-10-03; UA062.001.003.00039.00002; McGogh, Ken (Box 3)
      Athletics; Sports; Soccer (Men's); Dept. of Athletics
  - Sports: Soccer (women's), 1984; UA062.001.004.00001 (Box 4)
    - Women's soccer game, 1984; UA062.001.004.00001.00001; Thornton, Dan (Box 4)
      Athletics; Soccer (Women's); Sports; Dept. of Athletics
  - Sports: Softball, 1981; UA062.001.004.00002 (Box 4)
  - Sports: Squash, 1981 -- 1986; UA062.001.004.00003 (Box 4)
  - Sports: Swimming (men's), 1985; UA062.001.004.00004 (Box 4)
    - Men's swimming team sitting on bench, 1985; UA062.001.004.00004.00001; Ruckerman, Jack (Box 4)
      Athletics; Sports; Swimming (Men's); Dept. of Athletics
  - Sports: Swimming (women's), 1985; UA062.001.004.00005 (Box 4)
    - Women's swimming team with coach, 1985; UA062.001.004.00005.00001; Sackelman, Ellen (Box 4)
      Athletics; Swimming (Women's); Sports; Dept. of Athletics
  - Sports: Tennis (men's), 1982; UA062.001.004.00006 (Box 4)
    - Men's tennis team standing in front of net, 1982; UA062.001.004.00006.00001; Unknown (Box 4)
      Athletics; Sports; Tennis (Men's); Dept. of Athletics
  - Sports: Tennis (women's), 1980; UA062.001.004.00007 (Box 4)
    - Women's tennis team standing in front of net, 1980; UA062.001.004.00007.00001; Unknown (Box 4)
      Athletic fields; Sports; Tennis (Women's); Dept. of Athletics
  - Sports: Track (men's), 1982; UA062.001.004.00008 (Box 4)
    - Men's track team in sweatshirts, 1982; UA062.001.004.00008.00001; Unknown (Box 4)
      Athletics; Sports; Track (Men's); Dept. of Athletics
  - Sports: Track (women's), 1983; UA062.001.004.00009 (Box 4)
    - Women's track team running, 1983-10-17; UA062.001.004.00009.00001; McGogh, Ken (Box 4)
      Athletics; Sports; Track (Women's); Dept. of Athletics
  - Sports: Volleyball, 1981 -- 1983; UA062.001.004.00010 (Box 4)
    - Jessica Poppele hitting a volleyball, 1981; UA062.001.004.00010.00001; Landau, Steven (Box 4)
      Back of print reads: "Tufts Observer Issue; Photo# 21B Slug Poppelle; Credit Landau; Reduce 150% to 5 1/4x3 1/4; File Vball." A note taped to back of print reads: "Photo# 23c Slug W. Volleyball; Reduce 86%; Taken 81"
      Volleyball; photographic print; Poppele, Jessica
    - Wendy Weiss hitting a volleyball, 1981; UA062.001.004.00010.00002; Landau, Steven (Box 4)
      Back of print reads: "Tufts Observer Issue; Photo# 21A Slug Weiss; Credit Landau; Reduce 116% to 5 1/4x3 1/4; File V BALL"
      Volleyball; photographic print; Weiss, Wendy
    - Maria Cahill and Kristine Hunter playing volleyball, 1981; UA062.001.004.00010.00003; Landau, Steven (Box 4)
      Top of print reads: "PHOTOGRAPH BY STEVEN LANDAU". Back of print reads: "Cahill - foreground; Hunter - background"
      Volleyball; photographic print; Cahill, Maria; Hunter, Kristine
    - Women playing volleyball, 1983; UA062.001.004.00010.00004; Unknown (Box 4)
      Volleyball; photographic print
    - Women playing volleyball, 1983; UA062.001.004.00010.00005; Unknown (Box 4)
      Back of print reads: "Shoot at 76% adn 34%; R-76% ALSC R-34% 180:08"
    - Women playing volleyball, 1983-10-12; UA062.001.004.00010.00006; Florence, Mark (Box 4)
      Back of print reads: "Volleyball; Credit Mark Florence; 10/12/83"
    - Women playing volleyball, 1983-10-13; UA062.001.004.00010.00007; Florence, Mark (Box 4)
      Back of print reads: "18117 PAGE 112 pic#1; Volleyball; Credit Mark Florence; reduce 105%; 10/13/83; FLOP; E-105% .85 .10"
    - Women playing volleyball, 1983-09-08; UA062.001.004.00010.00008; Norris, Suzanne (Box 4)
      Back of print reads: "V-Ball; 9/8/83; Credit Suzanne Norris"
    - Women's volleyball team, 1981-11; UA062.001.004.00010.00009; Unknown (Box 4)
      Back of print reads: "Volleybal fall '81; MAIAW st. champions (11/81)"
  - Sports: Wrestling, UA062.001.004.00011 (Box 4)
  - Sprague, 1983; UA062.001.004.00012 (Box 4)
  - Spring Fling, UA062.001.004.00013 (Box 4)
  - Students (A), 1978 -- 1982; UA062.001.004.00014 (Box 4)
  - Students (B), UA062.001.004.00015 (Box 4)
  - Students (C), 1982; UA062.001.004.00016 (Box 4)
  - Students (D), 1981 -- 1982; UA062.001.004.00017 (Box 4)
  - Students (E), UA062.001.004.00018 (Box 4)
  - Students (F), 1979 -- 1983; UA062.001.004.00019 (Box 4)
  - Students (G), 1972 -- 1982; UA062.001.004.00020 (Box 4)
  - Students (H, I), 1982 -- 1986; UA062.001.004.00021 (Box 4)
  - Students (J), 1976 -- 1982; UA062.001.004.00022 (Box 4)
  - Students (K), 1978 -- 1989; UA062.001.004.00023 (Box 4)
  - Students (L), 1984; UA062.001.004.00024 (Box 4)
  - Students (M), 1978 -- 1982; UA062.001.004.00025 (Box 4)
  - Students (N), UA062.001.004.00026 (Box 4)
  - Students (O), 1986; UA062.001.004.00027 (Box 4)
  - Students (P), UA062.001.004.00028 (Box 4)
  - Students (R), 1980; UA062.001.004.00029 (Box 4)
  - Students (S), 1982 -- 1986; UA062.001.004.00030 (Box 4)
  - Students (T), 1982; UA062.001.004.00031 (Box 4)
  - Students (U, V), UA062.001.004.00032 (Box 4)
  - Students (W), 1980 -- 1986; UA062.001.004.00033 (Box 4)
  - Students (X, Y, Z), UA062.001.004.00034 (Box 4)
  - Students (Unidentified), UA062.001.004.00035 (Box 4)
  - Student Life, 1976 -- 1984; UA062.001.004.00036 (Box 4)
  - Torn Ticket, 1, 1985; UA062.001.004.00037 (Box 4)
    - Two student perfomers in 'Hair' performed by Torn Ticket II, 1985-11-14; UA062.001.004.00037.00001; McGogh, Ken (Box 4)
      Student activities; Theater; Musicals; Students; Torn Ticket Two
  - Torn Ticket, 2, 1988; UA062.001.004.00038 (Box 4)
    - 'Candide' performed by Torn Ticket II, 1988-11-10; UA062.001.004.00038.00001; Bushell, Steven (Box 4)
  - Train, 1983; UA062.001.004.00039 (Box 4)
  - Tufts Mountain Club, 1984; UA062.001.004.00040 (Box 4)
  - TUTV, 1981; UA062.001.004.00041 (Box 4)
  - Wessell Library, 1986; UA062.001.004.00042 (Box 4)
  - West Hall, UA062.001.004.00043 (Box 4)
  - Bob Winn, 1979; UA062.001.004.00044 (Box 4)
  - WMFO, 1977 -- 1983; UA062.001.004.00045 (Box 4)
- Observer article files, 1969 -- 1986; UA062.002; 3.6 Linear Feet
  This series contains newspaper clippings organized by subject headings. It also contains brochures, correspondence, reports, memoranda, minutes, promotional materials, newsletters, public statements, interviews, and articles published elsewhere. These article folders represent a partial collection of stories published by the Observer on select topics from 1970 to 1984. Topics include: academic issues, administrative issues, buildings, events, people, and student life. Some files include cross references to other topics.
  At the end of this series is a partial subject index to Observer articles from 1985-1986. Organization of the index is alphabetical, but "B" and "O" are missing. During processing this index was grouped with the series, Article files, since both articles and index probably served a research/reference function.
  This series is arranged alphabetically by title.
  - AAUP, 1984; UA062.002.005.00001 (Box 5)
  - Abortion, 1972 -- 1981; UA062.002.005.00002 (Box 5)
  - Accounting (University), 1980 -- 1981; UA062.002.005.00003 (Box 5)
  - Activism/Apathy, 1981; UA062.002.005.00004 (Box 5)
  - Ad Hoc Committee, 1981; UA062.002.005.00005 (Box 5)
  - Admissions, 1975 -- 1980; UA062.002.005.00006 (Box 5)
  - Admissions-Class of 1981, 1977; UA062.002.005.00007 (Box 5)
  - Admissions-Classes of 1982, 1983, 1984, 1978 -- 1980; UA062.002.005.00008 (Box 5)
  - Administration Shifts, 1978 -- 1979; UA062.002.005.00009 (Box 5)
  - Administration, 1980 -- 1981; UA062.002.005.00010 (Box 5)
  - Affirmative Action, 1970 -- 1981; UA062.002.005.00011 (Box 5)
  - Afghanistan, 1980; UA062.002.005.00012 (Box 5)
  - Afro Studies, 1973 -- 1978; UA062.002.005.00013 (Box 5)
  - Alcoholism, 1981; UA062.002.005.00014 (Box 5)
  - Alumni, 1970 -- 1981; UA062.002.005.00015 (Box 5)
  - Animal Clinic, 1981; UA062.002.005.00016 (Box 5)
  - Antiwar Activities, 1970 -- 1973; UA062.002.005.00017 (Box 5)
  - Arena Bubble, 1974; UA062.002.005.00018 (Box 5)
  - Arts Commission, 1980; UA062.002.005.00019 (Box 5)
  - Barnum-Dane Fire, 1975 -- 1978; UA062.002.005.00020 (Box 5)
  - Bay Bank/Middlesex, 1971 -- 1977; UA062.002.005.00021 (Box 5)
  - Bio Med Science School, 1980; UA062.002.005.00022 (Box 5)
  - Biosciences Program, 1977 -- 1978; UA062.002.005.00023 (Box 5)
  - Blizzard of 1978, UA062.002.005.00024 (Box 5)
  - Bradford Hotel, 1977 -- 1979; UA062.002.005.00025 (Box 5)